[{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975063199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9475,"timeElapsed":127844},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975066023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2822,"timeElapsed":130668},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975068859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2834,"timeElapsed":133504},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975071285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2424,"timeElapsed":135930},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975075795,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4508,"timeElapsed":140440},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975078292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2494,"timeElapsed":142937},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975081003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2710,"timeElapsed":145648},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975082965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1960,"timeElapsed":147610},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975085958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2990,"timeElapsed":150603},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975090174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2580,"timeElapsed":154819},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975092067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1893,"timeElapsed":156712},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975094167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2098,"timeElapsed":158811},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975096255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2086,"timeElapsed":160900},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975100227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3970,"timeElapsed":164872},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975102590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2361,"timeElapsed":167235},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975108183,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5592,"timeElapsed":172828},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975110272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2086,"timeElapsed":174916},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975112613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2341,"timeElapsed":177258},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975114732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2116,"timeElapsed":179376},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975118095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2233,"timeElapsed":182740},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975120049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1953,"timeElapsed":184694},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975122395,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2344,"timeElapsed":187039},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975124502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2105,"timeElapsed":189147},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975126506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2003,"timeElapsed":191150},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975129231,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2724,"timeElapsed":193876},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975132429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3196,"timeElapsed":197074},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975134403,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1972,"timeElapsed":199048},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975136429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2024,"timeElapsed":201074},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975138718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2286,"timeElapsed":203363},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975142075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2478,"timeElapsed":206720},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975143953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1876,"timeElapsed":208598},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975146039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2084,"timeElapsed":210684},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975147839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1799,"timeElapsed":212483},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975149534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1692,"timeElapsed":214179},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975151561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2027,"timeElapsed":216206},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975153349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1787,"timeElapsed":217994},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975156276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2925,"timeElapsed":220921},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975158110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1833,"timeElapsed":222755},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975162249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2617,"timeElapsed":226894},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975164184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":1933,"timeElapsed":228829},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975166131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1946,"timeElapsed":230776},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975167796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1664,"timeElapsed":232441},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975170065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2267,"timeElapsed":234709},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975172063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1995,"timeElapsed":236708},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975173757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1694,"timeElapsed":238402},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975175595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1835,"timeElapsed":240240},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975177527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1931,"timeElapsed":242172},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975181049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2155,"timeElapsed":245694},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975184087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3037,"timeElapsed":248732},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975185836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":1746,"timeElapsed":250481},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975187809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1972,"timeElapsed":252454},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975189497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1686,"timeElapsed":254142},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975191312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1814,"timeElapsed":255957},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975193161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1848,"timeElapsed":257806},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975195015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1851,"timeElapsed":259659},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975196680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1664,"timeElapsed":261325},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975199859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2085,"timeElapsed":264504},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975201454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1593,"timeElapsed":266098},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975203243,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1787,"timeElapsed":267888},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975204817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1572,"timeElapsed":269462},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975206595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":1776,"timeElapsed":271240},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975208275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1679,"timeElapsed":272920},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975210957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2681,"timeElapsed":275602},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975212873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1915,"timeElapsed":277518},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975214518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1643,"timeElapsed":279162},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975218326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2504,"timeElapsed":282971},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975220008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":1681,"timeElapsed":284653},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975221709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1700,"timeElapsed":286354},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975223419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1709,"timeElapsed":288064},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975227178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3756,"timeElapsed":291822},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975229133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1955,"timeElapsed":293778},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975230917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1782,"timeElapsed":295562},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975232799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":1881,"timeElapsed":297444},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975235312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2511,"timeElapsed":299957},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975238752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2705,"timeElapsed":303397},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975240194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1442,"timeElapsed":304839},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975241849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1653,"timeElapsed":306494},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975243297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1446,"timeElapsed":307942},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975244781,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1484,"timeElapsed":309426},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975246385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1602,"timeElapsed":311030},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975248055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1668,"timeElapsed":312700},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975249807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1751,"timeElapsed":314452},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975251743,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1934,"timeElapsed":316388},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975256549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3812,"timeElapsed":321194},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975258082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1532,"timeElapsed":322727},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975259823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1739,"timeElapsed":324468},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975261545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1720,"timeElapsed":326190},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975263696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2150,"timeElapsed":328341},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975265646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1948,"timeElapsed":330291},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975267228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1578,"timeElapsed":331873},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975269016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1787,"timeElapsed":333661},{"subjectID":"5jd4x5mxgf","prolificID":"6759ab1afbc694cb6937cac3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7d7ae2b3b5644c5801","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975270856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1838,"timeElapsed":335501}]